{
    "id": "1b9c936a46e945b58b7ed5225f1231aa",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise | Prepositions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We climbed ……………….. the hill with great difficulty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e52d02ebc3a6495caa554d9eadadc3a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Distribute these toffees ...................... these two boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d6d00da80af445bd81831b93ac2320f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Riches are a source ....................... great distress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e00c2906d93c4ee89ad358f0b076435f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cut your coat according ..................... your cloth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa1bcb08295e49c4b9a720a4dbd1e7ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should try to live ..................... our means.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "within",
                "with in",
                "beyond"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a5c24c132a8048af87c255129ed62aba"
        },
        {
            "question": "A man is known …………………. the company he keeps.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "48b8a06f6acb4007b3f8ed98b31d607c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was born ..................... noble parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d9e3a94863e549a48b4d532ff6b1acca"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lion pounced ………………… the deer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0286595993964c47bb1021403f6f2e16"
        },
        {
            "question": "This way, you can kill two birds ………………….. one stone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5df477dfc3ac4a15a0668e08fe6dc3f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was killed ………………….. the robber ………………….. a sword.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by, by",
                "by, with",
                "with, with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5baf2e88468c40a3823ed95408ec34eb"
        }
    ]
}